[
  {
    "question": "Bonne journée (bun zhoor-nay)",
    "answers": ["Goodbye", "Have a good day", "Welcome", "Good evening"],
    "correctIndex": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "À bientôt (ah bee-ahn-toh)",
    "answers": ["Good night", "See you soon", "And you?", "Until next time"],
    "correctIndex": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "À tout à l’heure (ah too tah luhr)",
    "answers": [
      "See you in a bit (if meeting later the same day)",
      "Hi/Bye (casual)",
      "I’m doing well, thank you.",
      "Delighted to meet you"
    ],
    "correctIndex": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "Au revoir (oh ruh-vwahr)",
    "answers": ["Hello/Good day", " See you tomorrow", "Goodbye", "How are you?"],
    "correctIndex": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "Ça va bien, merci (sah vah bee-ahn, mehr-see)",
    "answers": ["Have a good day", " See you tomorrow", "I’m doing well, thank you", "How are you?"],
    "correctIndex": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "À demain (ah duh-mahn)",
    "answers": ["Until next time", "Have a good evening", "See you tomorrow", "Not bad"],
    "correctIndex": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "Bienvenue (bee-ahn-vuh-noo)",
    "answers": ["I’m doing well, thank you", "Welcome (as in, welcome to this place)", "See you in a bit (if meeting later the same day)", "See you soon"],
    "correctIndex": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "À la prochaine (ah lah pro-shen)",
    "answers": ["Delighted to meet you", "Until next time", "Not bad", "See you soon"],
    "correctIndex": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "Enchanté(e) (ohn-shahn-tay)",
    "answers": ["Hello/Good day", "See you tomorrow", "Delighted to meet you", "No worries"],
    "correctIndex": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "Pas mal (pah mahl)",
    "answers": ["I don’t know", " See you tomorrow", "Not bad", "No problem"],
    "correctIndex": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "Comment allez-vous? (kom-mohn-tah-lay-voo)",
    "answers": ["How much?/How many?", "Can you help me?", "How are you? (formal/plural)", "What is it?"],
    "correctIndex": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "À plus tard (ah ploo tahr)",
    "answers": ["I’m doing well, thank you", "See you later", "Delighted to meet you", "Good evening"],
    "correctIndex": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "Bonne soirée (bun swah-ray)",
    "answers": ["Have a good evening", "Until next time", "Hello/Good day", "See you soon"],
    "correctIndex": 0
  } 
]

